This for everyone for
fundraising okay There's this
concept that I learned
and we developed at
early on called walking
up the then down
the What this means
is that most founders
they're go for the
biggest names VCs first
They go for like
the hottest names They
go for like people
who have like good
signal right But those
people are at the
top of the ladder
We encourage founders to
walk up the first
So you go for
other folks who are
like you and maybe
there's like a new
VC in and then
they just raised like
a small pocket of
but they're you they're
to Like get some
of these newer names
first Maybe there certain
angels whatever Like in
multiple rounds you can
still get angels involved
Angels like I customers
or something So you
kind of stack up
And some of these
like they could even
be like we've gotten
a of Taiwanese capital
into Southeast Asian startups
recently Like we've always
had a great relationship
with Taiwan and VCs
And so maybe you
get some of the
who are like say
not the usual suspects
Now if you start
stacking up let's say
you're raising 2 million
right And you got
like one and million
dollars from all kinds
of then you go
to the name that
you want And you
say hey Studio 65
VC I have half
my round of my
3 closed You want
to get in or
not Yeah you and
we're closing out the
rest of the tough
pretty soon but somebody
recommended I speak to
you right My friend
who is your profile
company environment I speak
to you but we
don't have too much
time But just you
know wanted to just
take up on this
thing right